Jason Lengstorf: 让我们创建一个布局文件，就像我们刚才说的那样
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Let's create that
layout file that we just said was going
存在。
to exist.
所以这将是源代码组件 layout.js。
So that's going to be at
source components layout.js.
Js 的源代码组件。
Source components layout.js.
在这里面我要进口反应从反应。
And inside of this I'm going
to import react from react.
你可能已经注意到我实际上并没有安装 react Gatsby 或者
And you may have noticed that I haven't
actually installed react Gatsby or
对这个主题做出反应。
react Dom in this theme.
那是因为它来自安装它的网站。
That’s because it’s coming from
the site that installs it.
您可以将它设置为一个对等依赖项，这可能是一个很好的实践。
You can set it up as a peer dependency and
that’s probably a good practice.
因为我知道一个事实，主题开发正在使用它
Because I know for
a fact that the theme dev is using it and
任何盖茨比的网站都会有盖茨比的反应。
any Gatsby site is gonna have
Gatsby react and react dom.
这不是严格要求的。
It’s not strictly required.
如果它不在那里，它就会破裂。
If it’s not there, it’s gonna break.
所以我要依靠父主题来创建布局。
So I'm gonna rely on the the parent
theme to have it create a layout.
这个布局将接纳孩子们。
And that layout is gonna receive children.
这就是内容。
That's the the content.
我们只要放出一个反应片段，里面会有一个标题。
And we'll just put out a react fragment
and that will have a header in it.
标题只会显示主题的名称。
And the header will just
say the name of the theme.
我们不是为了设计奖而来。
We're not going for design awards here.
我们将建立一个主要组件来接收孩子们。
And we'll set up a main component
that will receive the children.
将其作为默认值导出。
Export that as our default.
我们应该开始做生意了。
And we should be in business.
让我们继续运行这个程序，看看会发生什么。
So let's go ahead and
run this and see what happens.
所以我要纱线工作空间主题开发。
So I'm gonna yarn workspace
theme-dev develop.
我希望它读取 index.mdx 和
And what I expect to happen is that
it's going to read this index.mdx and
我将能够得到它的内容在我们的 graphQL 层。
I'll be able to get the content
of it in our graphQL layer.
那么，让我们来运行它。
So let's run it.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 现在我们还没有创建任何页面,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: And
now we haven't created any pages,
我们还没有告诉盖茨比使用这些数据。
we're not telling Gatsby
to use the data yet.
我们刚刚把它添加到数据层，这意味着如果我们看看我们的
We've just added it to the data layer,
which means that if we look at our
页面，就像我们的开发网站，仍然没有什么。
page, like our development site,
there's still nothing there.
但是 Gatsby 给了我们访问 graphQL 层的权限。
But Gatsby gives us access
to the graphQL layer.
所以我可以进入这个 graphql 层
So I can go into this graphql layer and
我现在可以看到，我们已经得到了所有文件和所有 MDX 的东西。
I can now see that we've got
things like all file and all MDX.
让我们看看这些 MDX，看看里面有什么。
So let's take a look at this all MDX and
see what's in here.
所以我想看看前面的问题和题目。
So I wanna see maybe the frontmatter and
the title.
杰森 · 兰斯托夫: 好了，现在我们有了我们的主页。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Okay,
so we've got our homepage.
它出现了。
It's showing up.
它在做我们想做的事。
It's doing what we want.
如果我得到了 HTML，Jason Lengstorf: 对不起,
And if I get the HTML,
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Sorry,
这是错的。
that's the wrong.
这叫身体，这是我的错。
It's called body, that's my mistake.
现在我们有了这个身体，这个有点时髦，对吧？
So now we've got this body, and
now this is a little funky, right?
这是下面的内容，但 MDX 有点包装了所有这些东西。
This is the content down here but MDX has
kinda wrapped all this stuff around it.
这就是我们进入布局的地方。
And that's where we get
into the layouts there.
Mdx 正在做很多事情
And MDX is doing a bunch of stuff so
我们可以执行反应内的 MDX 内容。
that we can execute react
inside of MDX content.
但是我们真的不需要担心这一部分，因为有一个帮手
But we don't really need to worry about
this part because there's a helper that
我们一会儿再来处理这件事。
we'll get to in a minute
that handles this for us.
如果你只是想检查里面有什么，我们可以做原始的身体。
If you just want to check what's in there,
we can do the raw body.
如果你想验证这一点的话，这会告诉我们文件的内容
And that'll show us just the contents
of the file if you want to verify that
有东西在那里。
something's there.
所以，我认为，这是一个承担我们工作的好地方。
So that, I think,
is a good place to commit our work.
所以，让我们再一次，只是得到一切。
So let's again, just get at everything.
再检查一遍。
Check that again.
好吧，这就是我们想要的，所以我们会承诺。
Okay, that's all we wanted so
we will commit.
Jason Lengstorf: Dev 和我们添加或加载 MDX 到 GraphQL。
&gt;&gt; Jason Lengstorf: Dev and
we added or load MDX into GraphQL.